♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ next Sunday, A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy
named Joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ he did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ so they shot him
into space ♪
♪ we'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
- ♪ the worst we can find ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
- ♪ and we'll monitor
his mind ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
- ♪ where the movies
begin or end ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot
friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
- ♪ cambot ♪
- ♪ gypsy ♪
- ♪ hi, girl ♪
- ♪ Tom Servo ♪
- ♪ what a cool guy ♪
- ♪ crow ♪
- ♪ what a wisecracker ♪
♪ you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
- ♪ and other science facts ♪
- ♪ la la la ♪
♪ then repeat to yourself,
"it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really
just relax" ♪
♪ for "mystery science
theater 3000" ♪♪
A one, a two.
We know what to do.
♪ We're the satellite of love
on the satellite of love ♪
♪ in spite of our situation
we're just fine ♪
♪ so forget about rejoicing
and pray for magic voice ♪
- It's 30 seconds
to commercials time.
- ♪ wee hoo! ♪
♪ So a couple of dumpy overlords
have shot us into space ♪
♪ we'll take this
stupid experiment ♪
♪ and jam it in their face ♪
- ♪ crow ♪
- ♪ gypsy ♪
- ♪ Servo ♪
- ♪ Joel ♪
- Stories, fun, toys!
- Whoo!
♪ We don't care,
don't despair ♪
♪ we're not wearing
our underwear ♪
♪ we're on
the satellite of love ♪
- ♪ warriors on the war-- ♪
- my marks!
All right. The best thing
about performing
is having the rocking
wrap party afterwards.
- Whoo!
- All right.
- Good idea.
And then when you're
done with him, Tom,
it's time for my backrub
and then, we sauna.
Hey, I'll give you a backrub as
soon as I'm done with crow here.
No, I'll give you both a backrub
when Tommy's done with me.
I'm going to put on Bette midler
so we can dance.
- Yay!
- Oh, great idea!
Hey, and then we can all
go down to the piano bar
- at nye's and...
- Sing showtunes!
- All right!
- Whoo hoo!
All right.
The evil impresarios
are calling, you guys.
Well, weenie buns,
I think we've
really outdone
ourselves this time.
Not only have we found
a movie
that will make
your toes curl,
but your shoes and
socks as well.
[Chuckling]
I thought the composting
toilet had backed up.
As it turns out,
it's this week's experiment!
- [Cackling]
- Whoo ooh!
Hey, Joel.
- [Sniffs] Ahh.
- Ahh.
But first, let's have at that
invention exchange, hmm?
Uh... um...
I'll be right back.
[Sighs]
Well, should we
show 'em ours?
Oh, yeah, good plan.
Um, hey, sirs,
we have our own
invention this time.
Cambot, move it in here.
Right here in my hand,
cambot, you see it?
- See?
- You see,
it's a new long distance
telephone transducer
that operates at seven ohms
and a nominal temperature range
of zero to 50 degrees celsius.
Yeah, it's a marked improvement
over the old configuration
that often required
over 25 seconds
to connect
transcontinental signals
and it does so
at half the cost.
And it's completely
solid state.
You see, the chip
sees a telephone signal
as a series of
ones and zeros, which are--
hey, guys, I found it.
Here's
the invention exchange.
It's called the big head.
Uh, Joel, we did
the big head already.
- Really?
- Yep, uh-huh.
- Uh-huh.
- Yes.
Uh, well, let's press on,
dingleberry.
- Our ex--
- say, who's that guy
with the big head?
Cork it, Larry.
Our experiment this week
is in honor of your
horribly stinky film.
Now, we all remember
and love the antics
of comedian Joe Besser
on the old "abbott
and costello" show.
Well, we can relive
those moments
with my new stinky bomb.
Yes, now you can turn
any friend
into that lovable buffoon
who was a lisping
man-child
long before
it became fashionable.
I think it would go
something like this.
Oh!
Elegant, isn't it?
Oh, I'll harm you!
Well, Joel, it's time for me to
send you your own stink bomb.
This film makes "the unearthly"
look like "citizen Kane."
- I'll give you
such a pinch!
- Ow!
It's called "the castle
of fu manchu." Oh!
Take a tall drink
of gray water, Joel.
It'll help you
get in the mood.
- Start the film.
- What if I don't wanna?
I don't wanna! Ow!
Oh, I'll harm you!
Now, are you posit--
oh, we start movie time!
Let's go!
I didn't know we had done
that one already.
- Yep.
- Yeah, we--
oh, look, it's filmed
in Oakland.
- Hey.
- What a wonderful lenten sky.
- This is fu manchu.
- And you're not!
Once again,
the world is at my mercy.
Mercy!
...not only the mysteries
of the continent,
but now of the oceans too.
And the ancient
secret of ventriloquism,
now you can too.
In the tropical waters
of the south Atlantic,
my hand stretches out
to turn water into ice.
Oh, he's a refrigerator.
...safety into
the deadliest peril.
Kind of like
a corvair, huh?
In a few moments,
the proof of my mastery
will be complete.
But first, this word
from Maxwell house.
Oh, they stole this from
a Titanic movie. Look.
O-73.
We use children
to grind our hops.
- Three cherries.
- Ding ding ding.
- Number five in.
- I know what this is.
It's a Chinese
personal computer.
- Well said.
- Real portable.
They must use ninja
dolphin temps.
There's no danger
of overload.
I did not ask.
...made a mistake.
Generate more energy
than we need.
I'm mixing my album,
leave me alone.
...stole his safety lock.
- Oh, he's kool fu moe g.
- [Beatboxing]
No, he's wearing
David byrne's big suit.
- Check it out.
- How about that.
- Big pajamas.
- When this lever reaches
the bottom of the groove,
we are at safety maximum.
Then let your foot
off the clutch.
...take the lever
and move it down
into the second groove
for the auxiliary
channels will feed in.
Auxiliary?
[Gasps]
He's flatlining!
- [Whistles]
- Phase two are coming in...
Now.
Uh, any time, come on in.
Phase two,
ladies and gentlemen.
Jiggle the plug.
Sometimes you gotta kick it.
The signal isn't
getting through.
- Hmm.
- Strengthen the signal.
- No!
- Do as I say!
Strengthen it!
Listen, my name is
on your check, buddy.
- Oh, it's a quad system.
- Oh.
We still have
the safety valve.
Hey, don't get your tie
stuck in that thing.
That's the biggest rock
tumbler I've ever seen.
Big wheel keep on turning.
[Imitates foghorn]
Uh, do we have to see this?
- No! We cannot!
- You will do it!
- No, no, no!
- Push the lever!
- No, you push the lever!
- I won't do it!
[Arguing at once]
It's "witness"
all of a sudden.
[Chuckling]
- Slide that lever over!
- Hmm?
Slide it over
and pull on it!
- That girl!
- Ooh.
- Like this?
- Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
[Imitates foghorn]
- [Gunshot]
- Oh, she exploded.
- Oh.
- Oh, thought she...
Looks like my freezer.
You should do
something about that.
Deploy the bread.
Wonder bread.
Lucy must be around here
somewhere.
- [Chuckling]
- "Ricky, I hit an iceberg."
Ah, call it quits.
That pretty much screws up
the shuffleboard.
Come on.
Hey, the water got warmer
in here.
Thank you, wang,
that'll be all.
Nose to the grindstone, you.
Oh, somebody wet the bed.
[Chuckling]
So I called down
to the desk clerk.
I said I had a leak
in the sink,
he said, "go ahead,
the customer's always right."
Ahh!
[Vocalizing "sabre dance"]
Uh-oh.
Women, children,
spacemen, Indians,
and sort of idealized
representations
of 16th century
flemish merchants first!
Kathie Lee, no!
Boy, these people really
know how to party.
Whoo!
It's a carnival cruise.
In a few moments,
the entire ship
will have vanished
beneath the ocean.
Ping, ping, ping.
This is the destiny
of fu manchu.
- And you are there.
- [Screaming]
And now back
to our channel 9 movie,
"the Poseidon adventure."
[Vocalizes]
[Imitates singing underwater]
- Ooh...
- Ahh!
- [Vocalizes "sabre dance"]
- Ooh!
Ahh!
[Imitates blowing
bubbles underwater]
Sliders.
Ooh.
- Huh?
- D'oh!
D'oh, gilligan, oh!
Skipper!
- Follow me!
- Come, let's have
a quick one.
- A cocktail.
- Ah, whee!
Waiter, waiter, we'll have
the Buddha delight,
pronto. Yeah.
Lousy service.
[Imitates singing underwater]
And there she goes. Yay!
- Well, that made no sense.
- Mm-mmm.
Epilogue.
Well, rocky, it turns out
that Jimmy was hiding
in the Camaro.
Now it's "adventures
in paradise."
♪ Fu manchu ♪
♪ a real bad man
with a plan ♪
♪ that's fu ♪
♪ he's the clown
in the robe ♪
♪ stands 'bout
seven foot two ♪
I'll have the number six,
the Christopher Lee.
It comes
with an egg roll.
In?
- Yes?
- In what?
- [Humming to music]
- Oh.
Oh, rohmer.
He's the guy who did
"my night at maud's."
- No, that's Eric rohmer.
- Oh.
Castle of fu manchu,
where you eat square hamburgers
with chopsticks.
Huh?
You know,
they should have stuck
Martin up there
with Crawford.
Then everyone
would have two names.
Hey, look, it's Howard and
Marion from "happy days."
Richie's parents.
♪ Taboo ♪
Richard Greene
is nayland Smith.
♪ Ba dum bum boom ♪
Wool provided
by Manuel merino.
♪ Fu manchu ♪
Oh, camilleri.
I love it with a light
horseradish sauce.
- That's calamari.
- Oh.
I always make that mistake.
♪ My lord, I'm bored ♪
♪ with these credits
already ♪
Aw, come on. We can't keep
making fun of the names.
Get on with it.
Titles by Peter Max.
Are these
the same towers or, uh...?
Oh, look, even the towers
got their own credits.
[Chuckles]
♪ By Harry Alan towers ♪
♪ Harry Alan towers ♪
♪ Harry Alan
towers! ♪
Last week
on "grizzly Adams"...
Hey, it's gadabout gaddis,
the flying fisherman.
Before babe winkelman,
there was gadabout gaddis.
I've got a bite!
Oh, cripes, you need
a lazy ike on there, I think.
I've got a real monster
this time.
This isn't
Loch Ness, petrie.
- You want a hand?
- No, I can make it.
This is a private trip.
Good job, you caught a tree
with that little fish.
- That's not bad.
- Bravo, petrie.
[Blusters]
Yes, all right,
I must say--
it's amazing
how these British
blend into their natural
environment, isn't it, now?
After landing that monster,
you must be hungry.
Let's open
the picnic basket.
Uh, Ted, your medication.
Did you take the pills
in Monday's little container?
Look at this guy.
Who's dressing him today?
- [Chuckling]
- Hello. What's this?
Probably fresh
salmon sandwiches.
Iceberg in the tropics?
What did you say?
Listen.
"Liner strikes iceberg.
- Hundreds drown."
- Good god, where?
- In the water!
- In the Caribbean!
Icebergs in the Caribbean?
This paper's a week old.
- So's the sandwich!
- Ah, something always happens
when we're on holiday.
Nayland Smith.
Petrie.
- Dish!
- Hello.
Well, petrie, old man...
[Blusters]
Hello, Chester,
what brings you here?
- My bicycle.
- Telegram.
Looks rather urgent.
♪ Ta-ra ta-ra-ta-ta,
Harry and the kids are dead ♪
♪ Harry and the kids are ♪
Thank you, curt.
It was very kind of you
to come.
Well, I didn't mean to,
but the new seat covers are--
not now!
Oh...
Fish aren't biting well
today, petrie, huh?
Everybody
can't be an Isaac--
don't wave your little
sizzler at me, dad.
Though we may be joining you
on the London train.
I'm here for the
"old gringo" audition.
Sounds like he got a little
shot of testosterone there.
We've got
another week yet.
Holidays are over,
petrie.
This is from
the home secretary.
We're ordered back
to London at once.
Oh, well,
that's our home secretary.
Hey, now it's Thomas
the tank engine.
[Imitates train chugging]
This is symbolic of their
return to London.
Meanwhile,
in downtown ames, Iowa.
In Chicago, on Grant park
in lakeshore drive,
- the field museum.
- [Beeping]
Our lunch today will be
toasted cheese sandwiches,
tomato soup, Turkey tidbits
and tater tots.
Stand by for an important
message from fu manchu.
How long have these messages
been coming in, sir Robert?
Oh, that's a rather personal
question, isn't it?
At first, we didn't take them
very seriously. But now...
Is the wavelength
being monitored?
- Yes, of course.
- [Mimics gunshot]
His finger went off.
That bastard's speaking
through our omelet pan!
This is fu manchu.
- And I'm an alcoholic.
- Hi, fu.
I gave a demonstration
of the new and
destructive weapon.
Hello! Hey!
Lights, please.
...the world has
two weeks to decide...
You know, it kind of looks
like a "nova" special
- on conception, doesn't it?
- Yecch.
...to my orders or...
- Or?
- Focus!
Something.
- We're green!
- They're green.
- Huh?
- Not again.
If disaster is
to be avoided,
I shall insist on
complete cooperation.
I shall give
no further warning.
But unless the heads of state
of the major powers--
looks like fu shops
at Ethan Allen.
Tasteful.
In 14 days from now,
I shall strike.
Does that start today?
Is that 14 business days
or would that be weekdays?
Uh, fu, this is
the riverboat queen.
We'll catch ya
on the flip-flop.
Catch ya later,
good buddy.
Ht and 10-4.
Fu manchu hasn't lost
his cunning.
He's used at least
four transmitters.
Impossible to trace.
He's threatened mankind
with obliteration.
It sounded almost biblical.
That's one book in which
you won't find fu manchu's name.
- Quite.
- I was thinking of a flood.
In some way, fu manchu's
new weapon
involves water
and its temperature.
Ooh, staring contest
on the left. Check it out.
- You blinked.
- ...In a spot where
he could control
great quantities
of water.
- Panama, Gibraltar--
- Grady falls.
- Or even--
- Wisconsin dells.
- The upper dells.
- Ooh, let's go there now!
Oh, sure, just barge
right into Istanbul.
- Oh, that's terrible.
- It's not Constantinople.
- Oh, no.
- ♪ Istanbul is
Constantinople ♪
♪ Hey, Mr. Rothstein ♪
Rula lenska as the Turkish
lieutenant's woman.
Gee, I don't recognize him,
but the Fez is familiar!
Ba boom.
Either I'm weird or
that guy's really hot.
Oh, it's Annie hall.
♪ La Dee dah la Dee dah ♪
Bet he's smoking
a camel, huh?
- Ooh!
- Turkish and domestic blend.
It's like a meeting
of the shriner mafia.
Do you like this pole?
This water spreads out.
- What?
- In search of the sun.
I have been sent by my--
there goes a sneaky sub.
Good. We have
no time to waste.
Yeah. Whatever.
Hey, look, pac-man's
got his own flag!
We're just two ships
passing in the-- uh, day.
[Chuckles]
[Imitates musical horn]
Catalina camper ride.
Are you following me?
Quit following me.
Heel. I don't want
you following me.
All we are is dust
in the wind, man.
That's so true.
♪ I have often walked down
this road before ♪
Well, you see the theories
are harder to see
when you sneak
around like that.
Next we travel to Istanbul
with Robert goulet
as he tokes up
with adnan khashoggi.
Jeannie?
Master,
I have brought the lady.
Oh, wow, I'm so high.
Excuse me
while I kiss the sky.
Persistent lady.
Greetings.
Sit down, please.
I am sitting down.
You have received
my message?
What have you to sell me?
- Opium.
- Hmm.
I have enough opium.
How about Chanel no. 5?
...to control the trade
of half of the world.
You are starting
to interest me.
You are one of the few--
the proud, the marines.
Yes.
The governor's castle
contains
the biggest reserve
of opium in the east.
What are we
waiting for, then?
Road trip, dude! Whoa!
Very interesting.
If you agree,
we will share the opium.
- With her and her roommates.
- Explain to me your plans.
You will send your men
up the river bosphorus--
- we gotta go, guys.
- Let's get out of here.
...killing sentries
at the main gate,
leaving the way clear
for me and my men...
[Sobbing, sniffles]
Oh, uh, are we on?
[Clears throat]
"The miss Saigon syndrome,"
an editorial
by crow t. Robot.
"Dear miss, sir or madam,
I can no longer
sit idly by
on my
little robot haunches
and watch Caucasian actors
being continually cast
in non-Caucasian roles.
Christopher Lee's
portrayal of fu manchu
is a crystalline example of
the phenomenon I have tried,
titled bad actors,
bad decisions."
[Sniffles] Sorry.
"This insidious tradition
of casting
has formed
a psychological backup
in which we play out
the insignificant
comings and goings
of our daily lives.
Let me, crow t. Robot,
pull back the curtain
to reveal the lie
on which
your life is based.
Sign post number one on
your road to discovery--
George pal's enchanting
"the 7 faces of Dr. Lao."
Would it shock you to know
that all seven faces
were played by the white
musical theater actor
Tony Randall?
Wake up, people.
That's seven examples
right there.
Now you're saying to yourself,
"please, Mr. Robot,
carrier of the gleaming
sword of truth,
don't spoil the shiny obelisk
of Sunday afternoon enjoyment,
Charlie chan.
Sorry, it's my job.
Charlie chan is a Swede
named Warner oland!
Crow, stop now,
you're woozy!
No, the truth is
a runaway train.
Who's that playing
an Asian
in "the teahouse of
the August moon"?
It's your precious
method actor Marlon Brando!
Here's a bonus:
The Indian chief on "f troop"
was a grade-d actor
frank de kova.
Dare I go on?"
What's the point? [Sobbing]
Crow, buddy,
control yourself.
You're getting off track.
The kids out there love
your acerbic editorials
that stick it to the man.
You can't let them down.
- But it hurts too much.
- Buck up, crow!
Get out there and do it
for the kids. Come on!
[Both sobbing]
Okay. [Sniffles]
Anyway, where was I?
"So, in conclusion,
Cameron mackintosh, bite me."
Oh, wait--
"oh, there are so many
examples I should give.
What about Joey bishop
in "sergeants three"?"
Hey, wait a minute.
I liked Joey bishop
in that movie.
He's in a category
by himself.
He's always good, no matter
what role he plays.
Regis philbin
had no right to walk off
his show the way he did.
How could he do that?
Why? Why? Why?
No, no, no. [Sobbing]
- Joel, help us.
- [Both sobbing]
Look at what you've done
to my little friends.
Are you guys happy now?
Come on,
it's okay, buddy.
Don't you care?
Don't you even care?
Our data is showing deep,
deep pain all around.
Well, it looks like
we can expect
to get a nobel prize
for evil, frank.
[Laughing]
[Both cackling]
- [Gasping]
- [Laughing]
Better send them
a commercial.
[Wheezing]
- Oh, it's not that bad.
- It's really bad.
- Not more.
- Tell a joke.
Oh, Laurel and Hardy
are there.
- That's a good one.
- Give me a hammer.
I have a pass
to see the governor.
I was in "victor/victoria."
Here, let me see that.
"Please excuse Carol from--"
what is this?
Open the gates.
Now close it real fast.
D'oh!
"That girl!"
Oh, no, Bob hope
is killing people! Look!
Take that,
you fezzed monsters.
Pull!
- That's got flair.
- I guess that means
"come on."
Oh, Mrs. Peel,
we're needed.
Two stairs diverge
into a yellow wood.
Looks like Graceland.
Graceland!
- Memphis, Tennessee.
- Oh.
I see Elvis!
[Gasps] Where? Where?
Carry me, carry me.
Dog pile on him,
come on!
Tickle machine!
Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
Oh, bloodless guards.
- Thorazine guards.
- [Chuckles]
- ♪ Dum dum dum dum ♪
- oh!
Yawn.
- [Yelps]
- It's the killer joke!
Sure glad I dressed
to move, you?
Mm-hmm.
Jaw breaker.
- [Gasps]
- Chester a. Arthur!
Ooh, the Prez shot us
a buffalo there.
Mommy.
Boy, could you tell me
what day it is?
Why, it's Christmas day, sir!
[Shouting indistinctly]
Ruff, ruff, ruff!
- Grover Cleveland?
- Oh, there you are.
Oh, no!
[Shouting indistinctly]
- [Chuckles]
- Hey, who hasn't had
a nightmare like this?
My lord.
Oh. Oh,
it's you guys again.
Hello.
Moe, swords!
Smimitars!
My guards! Guards!
All right, everybody.
It's a b major.
He's being attacked
by a swing choir.
Kareem!
Oh, he's standing
on an office chair.
- Lin tang.
- Yes, father.
Hello, we are your
new neighbors.
May we borrow
some Pesto?
Proceed, daughter.
Okay.
If you don't look good,
we don't look good.
Oops. [Chuckles]
Sorry, I missed.
Eww.
And now the cast of
"my fair lady."
You have fought well.
We are grateful to you
for opening the doors to us.
- It was nothing.
- "Nathing."
We were able
to approach unseen.
We are very happy
to serve you.
Check, please.
Uh-oh.
Rat-ta-ta-ta.
Bob hope is "the mechanic."
- Hmm.
- Isn't she helpful?
Over there.
He's strict, that one.
Whoa, let me tell you.
I'll be over here
if you need me.
Bring them to my father.
And bring me
to an orthodontist.
I'll say.
She fights like a man.
But she breaks
just like a little girl.
We must kill them.
Ooh.
You may serve us yet.
- I serve only one master.
- But I'm good at it.
We shall see.
Take her away.
Karen Valentine!
She's a good egg.
Why do you keep her alive?
She's dangerous.
- I have my reasons.
- Okay, Mr. Ceo.
Filmed in Ivana trump's
bathroom.
- [Imitates flatulence]
- Ohh.
Whoops! The king's
on his throne.
This will make
an excellent headquarters.
And Omar pasha?
The governor is still
in residence.
I shall announce that the castle
was attacked by bandits.
The attack failed,
the bandits were liquidated.
Along with some factory second
naugahyde furniture.
We have one week.
You mean starting today,
not--
you mean including today?
Wait a minute now-- oh.
Meanwhile, on the hallowed
halls of whatsamatta u...
Continue checking
every hour.
Report to me anything unusual,
anything at all.
[Blusters]
Now, petrie.
Don't call me Fifi
at the office, dear.
...and an incompetent dolt.
Did you come all the way to
Scotland yard to tell me that?
You sweet talker.
...terribly excited,
but I just found this.
It's been on my old bookshelf
all these years.
It's called "crazy cook",
can you believe it?
Mm-hmm, the world's
top authority.
- Well, I dare say, petrie--
- dish.
Would you explain
why this book of yours
has suddenly become
so important?
Because his theory
may give us the clue
that we are desperately
searching for.
Well, you see,
he has a theory
that when the chemical
properties of ordinary water
are such that they lend
themselves to transformation--
I bet this clown has his
underwear on backwards.
...tampered with
and he goes on to say here--
why are they dubbing
the British?
I don't know,
this is terrible.
- Yes, he we are.
- [Blusters] Let's see.
"He grabbed her
heaving breasts--"
oh, sorry, my note.
...essence prepared
by the methods
which are not as yet
practicable to man
might dramatically change
his temperature to cold
so intense--
zzz. Help me! Zzz.
There now,
provided that you've got
a sufficient quantity
of water,
the pressure will build up
which will eventually,
with crystals,
become, as he says,
uncontrollable.
- Neat.
- But these crystals
of which he writes,
what will they be
composed of?
Possibly a derivative of--
are you Carol Burnett
all of a sudden?
- What is it?
- From Istanbul, sir.
Attack on the headquarters
of the governor of anatolia.
- They're all killed.
- I love you.
[Smooch]
What about the Bible
now, petrie?
The hand of Providence?
I don't understand.
- Anatolia--
- east of java.
...is the largest source
of supply
in the world
of the opium poppy.
By heavens,
I was right!
I love opium!
But first of all,
I want to have a word
with your professor
heracles.
I anticipated you'd try
to get in touch
with heracles
at the university.
He's gone on a trip
to the middle east in Turkey.
- Turkey!
- That's what I'm hungry for!
I want Turkey and Swiss!
Anatolia, perhaps.
And I told ya twice!
Meanwhile at gyro castle...
Just a typical morning
for Burt young.
Oh, here comes Peter O'Toole
and Albert Finney.
Hmm.
When you're serious
about weight loss...
Hi, sunshine. You look
bright-eyed this morning.
Read me a story.
Once upon a time,
there was a very naughty
man named fu manchu.
- Ooh.
- You will come
to the laboratory--
and he had a spooky-wooky
daughter.
- Ooh.
- I am perfectly well aware
of the condition
of your heart, professor.
However,
I can keep you alive.
Not forever.
I'm growing weaker,
in spite of your drugs.
I'm going to die.
There are ways
of persuasion.
I'm no use to you dead.
Within a week, perhaps before,
I shall be dead.
We shall see.
I'd like two espressos
over here, please.
Yes, my little friend drew
sent these over for you.
Ooh.
Wow, they make
strong drinks there.
He just injected it
into the mattress.
D'oh!
There now, give this back
to sid and Nancy.
You know, I'm learning
a lot more about
this guy's nasal hair
than I ever really
wanted to know.
- Me too. Yecch!
- Yuck.
You are going
to remain alive--
and stoned
off your flabby butt.
I understand you've consulted
a brilliant young specialist
last year.
What was his name?
Howser. Doogie howser.
He's in London,
but he would never help you.
He will save my life.
Indeed.
Not even Kessler
can save me.
Can't you understand?
My heart.
Becky, Tom,
are you in there?
- [Mimics echoing]
- It's dying.
Hmm?
Mosquito.
There are other
younger hearts in the world.
Dad. Like, I'm almost sure.
Gag me.
Stronger hearts.
Say, who's the new guy?
Jeez, he's had
his nipples sanded off.
Ooh! [Winces]
Does he please you?
Does he bring you pleasure?
Oh, sure, go ahead and barge
right into London.
It was funny
the first time.
We now return to
"those magnificent men
and their jaunty jalopies"
on your channel 9 movie.
[Humming classical music]
"Masterpiece theater" continues
with "the Jewel in the crown."
It's Audrey hepburn
in "charade."
You know, personally,
I would have worn
a slingback
with those shoes.
- You would?
- Yeah.
Did the director take his
lessons in walking scenes
from Roger corman?
Nobody's following you!
They switched
the toaster, I think.
I've been eating
berries all day.
Ooh, does she
or doesn't she?
The Dutch masters at home!
Yes, yes, yes, Mrs. Ward.
- No, no, no.
- No.
- Yes.
- No, no, no.
- Yes, yes, yes.
- Two pills every night
for a week.
- No.
- Yes.
- Yes?
- No.
- You don't say.
You don't say.
- Who was it?
- He didn't say.
- [Chuckling]
Thank you very much.
You don't have any more
patients, do you?
- No.
- I can't watch
another frame.
I'm afraid
I can't come yet.
Um, I'm expecting someone.
- Oh, someone important?
- Oh, yes.
Oh, boring.
...from the home office
and the others
from Scotland yard.
So, they've found you out
at last.
- Oh, yes. I--
- [knock on door]
- Hmm.
- Right on time.
Ingrid, I sent
miss Lawrence home.
- Would you?
- Of course.
- I'll also send
miss Lawrence home.
- Thank you very much.
And now time
for a bloody marry.
[Ringing]
Yes, that would be
the phone.
Dr. Kessler.
Who?
Not who, fu!
Oh, yes, sir Charles.
No, no, no, no.
No, I'm afraid I can't
attend the dinner tonight.
Right this way.
An important case, yes.
Very good. Now,
just put on the paper gown
and get in the stirrups,
thank you.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
We introduced ourselves.
Dr. Kessler,
this is Dr. Petrie.
Sir Dennis nayland Smith.
We're old friends.
We met on holiday.
We fished the same river.
[Blusters]
Balderdash.
Dr. Kessler,
we want some information
about professor heracles.
He is your patient,
isn't he?
Yes, patient and friend.
But he has a very severe
cardiac condition--
- so I don't like him anymore.
- Has something happened to him?
Do you know where he is now?
Well, here's a stab.
Joe's bar?
He called me last week
to tell me
he was going
to the continent.
No, no, you fool,
he's incontinent.
Oh, yes. Some days ago
I had a card from Athens.
- She turned into a mannequin.
- Hmm.
Look, I've got it
here somewhere,
- if I can just find--
- hmm, not bad.
Later, later.
Oh, now,
that's disgusting.
A picture of you
and Oliver Reed.
What the devil is he doing
so far from England?
He mentions on the card that
he's moving on to Istanbul.
Istanbul! What's he doing,
the circular trip?
- [Knock on door]
- Oh, Ingrid, uh--
get some more actors
in this scene, will you?
- Would you please tell--
- yes, yes, don't worry.
I'll send them away.
Let's not clue the audience in
on the plot yet, okay?
Let's ditch her, huh?
Would you like one
of our "watchtowers"?
Does this bug you?
I'm not touching you.
Calgon, take me away.
I know nothing about
heracles' experiments.
- Not at thing, not a thing.
- ...One thing, I'm sure.
He would want to--
to benefit mankind,
not to destroy it.
Fu manchu is only
interested in destruction.
Hey, he's making
a xerox copy of his butt.
Oh, what do you know.
I believe it's a question of
saving the world, Dr. Kessler.
Oh, that.
Leave the specimens
alone, please.
I think it would be fun
to go to Istanbul.
It would be fun.
...come with you.
And maybe Ingrid too.
- Good.
- Thank you.
We'll make it a holiday,
a camping holiday.
Damn, this tobacco
is really good.
[Knocking on door]
Only you can prevent
desk fires.
[With Asian accent]
Land shark.
Tickle ray.
Miss Jane pittman.
Time for go to bed.
I wonder
what's keeping Kessler.
Gee, this is the most action
we've seen so far.
Smells like a dead monkey
in here. You?
It's not funny
anymore, guys.
I can't take this anymore.
I gotta get out of here.
Please.
- Okay. Jeepers.
- Terrible!
...leave a cigarette burning
on a polished wood table.
Ah, come in, red shriner
sergeant-at-arms Joel.
This is black shriner leader
Tom.
Come in, boys,
and cut the comedy.
I'm in trouble here.
Over.
[Joel]
Uh, yeah,
shriner leader Tom,
this is red shriner Joel
at your back door
with neon peon crow in tow.
- What's your 20?
- What's my 20?
Sweet sons of Norway, man,
my magic carpet's malfunctioned
and I'm stuck in front
of the Robert hall store
on the main street.
On top of that,
I've run out of
jolly rancher candy
and the kids are starting
to look ugly, over.
[Crow]
Ace to you, good buddy.
This is the neon peon.
I'm in your rocking chair.
Hold tight, shriner leader.
Joel and I are about
to do a flyover.
Hurry up, man. I'm running
out of hard candy.
Condition red,
send in the clowns,
send in the--
oh, what's the use?
[Sobbing]
Oh, man, Joel,
he's totally off script.
There's nothing that says
anything about sobbing
like a broken man.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's see.
It says here, "Tom says,
'time formation, man.
Those kids are
all over me. Argh.'"
it just says "argh."
It doesn't say anything
about sobbing pitifully.
I can't do it, guys.
I just can't do it.
I can't go through
another sketch
loosely based on some
vague reference to the movie.
There are only a few guys
with fezzes in this movie
and suddenly,
we're the ziyara shriners
riding flying carpets
on mental street days.
Whaah! [Sobs] I can't do it!
Get me out of here.
I don't understand.
How is this sketch
any different
than anything else
we do during a movie?
Well, crow,
it's not the sketch,
it's this movie.
Look at him.
- He's just a broken man.
- You're telling me,
there are absolutely
no psychological footholds
in this film.
It's like trying
to climb El capitan.
There's something wrong
with me.
There's something
wrong with me. Why? Why?
- Better you than me.
- Oh, crow, come on.
Look at what you've done
to him.
Do you see what
you've done to this guy?
- Come on.
- [Hyperventilating]
You see, frank,
it feels good
to be with the winners,
doesn't it?
Oh, yes.
Hey, let's order out.
Mongolian?
I was thinking
more along the lines
of one of those delightful
stuffed Pesto pizzas
from Eduardo's.
Hmm.
You fly, I'll buy.
Solid, Jackson.
[Chuckling]
Oh, bite me. It's fun.
Thankee, Frankie.
Now, joely, you
and your scaredy bots
sup great deep drafts
of the second half
of this stinkburger
called
"the castle of fu manchu."
Ain't that a man?
Oh! We got movie time!
Let's hit it, boys!
[Joel]
Oh, it's okay.
[Tom crying]
...two abductions
in two countries.
Two coffees? [Sobs]
I know you will be able
to follow without any trouble.
Goodbye, melnik.
But I'm not leaving--
oh, I see.
You don't have to
knock me over the head.
- ...lieutenant, sir.
- I feel a little better.
- Go away.
- Order lunch.
- That'll take a while.
- Thanks, guys.
Go!
You need a tower of bricks
to fall on you?
Goodbye, sergeant.
- Ah!
Meanwhile, in east dubuque.
It's Nessie! No.
It's the boss!
It's Springsteen!
The boat!
The boat, Charles!
But keep it quiet!
We've got
a super secret plan!
Methinks the king
approaches.
Darn escalator's out again.
Got trapped on there once.
Lin tang arrives
with the prisoners!
They could use
an extension line.
I'm done tanning,
thanks.
Under this robe, I'm as naked
as the day I was born.
I'm riding free and easy.
[Laughing]
You don't think
there's much chance
he'll fall
down those stairs?
Uh, no.
Wishful thinking.
[Whispering]
One better.
Haikiba!
Suddenly, I have the urge
to, uh...
Shower.
What are you looking at?
We'll be right back
after this.
Come back here!
[Gasps]
Where are you going?
To scarborough fair?
I must see your master.
Get out of here!
Heh, that guy's
gonna be a sophomore
- for five years, man.
- Yep. Mm.
I bring you
valuable information.
I bring tidings
of great joy.
...is all I'm asking.
Stop talking and...
And start chalking.
Well, once upon a time,
there were three bears.
[Whispering]
Cher's getting back
with Greg allman.
[Gasps]
...in Istanbul.
She took two
prisoners away with her.
Justine Bateman has a new movie
coming out.
Yes, yes.
Of course, I do not know who,
but I know which...
Which way they went.
Well?
The same road Lisa took, master,
to the other side.
[Imitates kissing]
You smell like a fresh cookie.
- To anatolia.
- Yes.
You're dripping sweat on me.
Ahmed!
Reward him.
Oh, someone's got
an oily t-zone.
Where's his reward?
[Screaming]
No, no, I meant give him
a slice of pie.
I'm so wasted,
I forgot what he said.
- Always.
- No, never.
Ugh.
Oh, it's the Istanbul
orkin man.
Hmm.
I'd say this movie
has less action
than a "whose life
is it anyway?"
I'm a sailor.
[Whimpers]
Will you help me?
Hmm?
What, what?
What?
Ohh. No!
No! Oh...
Michael Caine and Nancy kulp
are vampires.
Shoot, roommates!
David bowie,
from "the hunger."
He's all dewy.
Dewy bowie.
I hate jetlag.
Boy, I really racked up
the frequent flier miles,
though.
Yeah, frequent dier miles!
[Laughter]
Jeez.
You're feeling better?
A little.
Kessler!
Ingrid!
In color!
She's kind of overdressed
for espionage.
Professor heracles.
[Grunts]
She had to sit next
to the stinky guy.
Eww, uck.
Oh, I can't watch this.
I mean,
I can't see this.
It's kind of like a metallica
video, but slower.
Come on, what is this,
kirlian photography?
Yeah, moe, Larry, and kirlian
photography.
Yeah, heh.
Jeez, and I thought "city of
hope" was an underlit movie.
Uck.
Ugh.
They've been candied!
- Candide?
- Candide.
Where are we?
You're one step away
from never working again.
Anatolia...
Near the bosphorus.
They've turned us
into warhols!
It's incredible.
What?
Who were those people?
[Imitating thurston howell]
Who are these people?
...kidnapped by the men
of fu manchu.
Fu man--
manchu,
spit it out, honey.
I can't move.
I feel I'm paralyzed.
You'll be all right
in a few minutes.
They used my crystals
against you.
The first color movie
that needs to be colorized.
But in a small dose.
[Groaning]
Professor!
Look, you're overtired.
We'll talk to you later.
Ah.
She could use
a good Clay pack.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, yeah.
Spores.
Ew.
Come on.
Meanwhile,
in downtown duluth.
That's not funny.
I went to Istanbul,
and all I got
was this lousy Fez, huh?
- Heh heh.
- That's funny.
Hey, take a long walk
off that thing.
Yeah.
Hi, we're the boatniks.
[Chuckles]
Inspector Hammond?
You inspect her, I'm busy.
An honor, sir.
But I'm afraid
that I have bad news.
What is the bad news,
inspector?
My hat.
The bandits, sir,
who attacked at the castle
were Omar pasha's men.
Omar pasha?
He controls the opium trade.
- The perfume?
- Opium?!
An informer called melnick
appeared this morning,
killed.
Bzz!
Tell me again, please.
I need your help,
please.
...to Omar pasha's coffee shop.
- ♪ Omar pasha ♪
- [chuckles]
I should have
listened to him.
Why?
Omar pasha has vanished.
Meanwhile in--
aw, forget it.
...that he has gone to anatolia
to rescue the girl Lisa
and is camped opposite
the castle on the other side...
Looks like two seals
waterskiing, doesn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Kinda?
No.
♪ Allah ♪
♪ oh, lord, it's hard
to be a mole ♪
[Chuckles]
Ah.
♪ Allah ♪
Uh-oh.
Hey, it's the grand wizard
himself.
- What a boring--
- wow.
[Chanting]
Ooh!
Agh!
- Come on!
- Thank you.
Thank you,
next show at 10:00.
Thank you very much.
Hey, uh, don't
step in the guy, heh.
Ugh.
- All is clear, master.
- Come on.
Oh, jeez, I thought shriners
helped people.
Rock the kasbah, dude.
Sharia don't like it.
Ah, wouldn't it be great
if we knew
who they were,
where they are,
or what they were doing?
Yeah, pretty much.
Well, he looks like a century 21
salesman.
Yeah, with that--
Gandhi's back,
and he's stuffed.
Fu manchu.
♪♪
Bring forth
the two prisoners.
Dr. Kessler
and Dr. Ingrid coch.
Yes, father.
The guards are
bringing them.
Oh, look, it's the original
hand-hammered wok.
Yeah, looks like stainless steel
from here.
Ohh... yeah, you're right.
Love me.
I have brought you here
to save
the life of someone
whose knowledge I require
as a thirsty
man needs water.
Tonight,
on "you asked for it"...
Clear water.
Crystal blue persuasion.
Ah, cripes, this again.
The name of the person to whom
I refer is professor heracles.
Uh, we're underwhelmed.
You know, Burt young
has looked worse.
Mm-hmm.
Well, he's Burt young,
all right.
- He is dying.
- Oh, professor.
You will use your skill,
doctor.
You will make him live.
Damn it, fu, I'm a surgeon,
not a doctor!
I am not a miracle worker.
Besides, you took everything
away except my hands.
On the contrary,
Dr. Kessler.
Et cetera, et cetera,
et cetera.
You will find everything here
that you require.
Let's see what's
behind door number one.
Ooh.
Here, I have
everything you need.
I threw in the hairy
naked man just for kicks.
Nice touch.
What's wrong with that man?
Nothing at all.
There is nothing wrong
with him, doctor.
He is in perfect
physical condition.
I'll say.
And, unlike
professor heracles,
his heart is sound
as a bell.
Bong!
Do you not agree, doctor,
that professor heracles
should have
that splendid heart?
Ah, if it comes
with that beefy chest!
- Ooh...
- Mm!
But that man is not dead
or dying.
He's only mostly dead!
He will die for the sake
of science.
And for your sake, also.
I need heracles
to complete my plans.
I need him alive--
conscious, coherent.
I wish this movie were conscious
and coherent!
[Laughing]
And if I refuse?
I hadn't thought of that.
Gosh, he's clever.
Then Dr. Ingrid coch
will die an extremely painful
death.
Oh good.
No!
Uh, fresh ground pepper
with that?
Mmm.
The choice is yours,
Dr. Kessler.
Well?
In order to convince you,
I shall arrange
a demonstration.
No!
No! No!
♪♪
What's going on?
Glen Manning,
get off that dam!
"Bridge on the river kwai."
Looks like it, doesn't it?
Biggest crack by a dam site.
- Doh!
- Ohh.
Right there.
Hey, there's a little
Dutch boy
putting his finger in there.
Where?
Run!
Run for your lives!
Run, men!
The plot's starting
to make sense!
Run!
- Run!
Oh, this dam scene.
Hey, don't forget
to punch out!
You know, um...
I suddenly have to go
to the bathroom.
- Really?
- Yep.
Why, I wonder?
Funniest thing.
- Ooh.
- You know, they might need
some Thompson's water seal
up there.
- Yeah, I think so,
to hold it back.
Don't worry, men.
It's the Egyptians
who are gonna get us.
Pharaoh and the gang.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Ooh.
[All cheering]
We're getting off early!
Whoo!
Free day!
"Force 10 from navarone."
Mm-hmm.
Oh, quit groveling.
Graveling?
[Man screaming]
Uh-huh.
Yep, yep.
Uh, you know,
cutting it faster
doesn't make it
any more exciting.
[All sigh]
Ohh, that's a relief.
I didn't think that dam
would ever break.
Huh-uh.
Oh, the rolling stones.
Doesn't do much for me.
Oh, oh. Oh.
Kind of convulsive,
isn't it?
Ha ha! You have got
to be kidding me, ha!
- They're very good.
"Prince of tides."
Yep.
Fu.
"The river," with Mel Gibson
and sissy spacek.
Fu.
You know, I miss the water slide
at the dells.
Yeah, I wanna--
fu.
Oh look,
rock me on the water.
[Man screams]
Really? Fu.
Complete annihilation.
I am the god
of hydrotherapy.
Even nayland Smith cannot
touch you now, father.
I wish that he would try.
We'll be back
after these messages.
Meanwhile, in two harbors,
Minnesota...
You must kill Kurtz.
Terminate with extreme
prejudice.
I was just...
[Blusters indistinctly]
This is Asia.
Uh, could we see specific sites
in Asia?
I must leave you gentlemen.
Thank you, inspector,
for all your help.
I'm sorry, petrie,
but this is where we part.
Speaking of part,
comb that hair.
It's better this way.
You can be
of more use in Istanbul.
Stuffed on a mantel.
I want you to telegraph the home
secretary's office in London.
Use the standard code.
Tell him that I intend
to try to get into
- fu manchu's castle.
- Yes.
But how do you know that
fu manchu captured the castle?
- Yeah.
- Besides, there's nothing
but guesswork to go on.
I have something here.
Wait, that's Robert goulet!
This was found
on a dead man.
Yech!
Ugh.
Still guesswork, petrie?
That's his head scarf!
[Speaks gibberish]
Curt, you mustn't do this.
Oh, very well, then.
I will use the toilet.
Ah, it can't be that bad.
They put them
in the same cell.
Yeah.
A doctor can't say no
to saving a life.
Except when the patient
has no insurance.
You cannot do this if,
by saving
professor heracles' life,
you are helping this murderer
in his plans.
Mm, classic tragedy, eh?
Do you believe that fu manchu
will let heracles live
after he's used him?
I don't know.
...much about that,
but I know what I like.
But we have
to try everything.
And nobody before tried to--
to do such an-- an operation.
You mean the goofy game
for dopey doctors?
Yep.
Do you...
...love me?
Do I what?
Do you think you can do it?
In the road?
- Oh, my...
- Yes.
Yes, I know we can do it.
Now that's lipstick
that lasts, from yardley.
I hope.
I'm so ashamed.
Are you sure...
...bees can fly?
...you're not doing this for me
just to save my life?
Well, look, I just wanted
to get to first base with you,
and things snowballed.
What?
Oh, were you talking?
Sorry.
We have not a chance.
In this moment...
You know, it's kind of
like watching
the "Hollywood squares."
- Yeah.
- Mm.
...who matters to me.
You are every woman
in the world to me.
[Approaching footsteps]
Have you been listening
the whole time?
I thought this
was a private cell.
Sneaky.
This scene is a real strain.
Yeah.
Well, that's great though.
- Just great.
- Great.
[Imitates clock ticking]
Yes, we know how long
this has been on.
Don't shove it
in our face.
Really.
Tonight on a very special
"Dr. Kildare"...
You say ether,
and I say eye-ther.
Let's call
the whole thing off.
Breathe deep
the gathering gloom.
Watch lights fade
in every room.
Oh, this is aromatherapy.
I've seen this before.
[Inhales]
Yep, more, more.
Keep it coming.
I can take more.
[Inhales]
Don't look at me!
Mommy! Mommy!
Frank booth.
Susie wong was arraigned
in Los Angeles county court
for impersonating
marlo Thomas.
I am susie wong.
[Deep voice]
No, I'm susie wong.
Will the real susie wong...
It's the world of susie wong.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, who wants a drumstick?
Ha, I'm just kidding.
Ha!
First we split the top,
then pour in real butter.
Mmm...
Ah.
- Oh, god!
- No!
Take it easy, it's just--
it's just tempera paint.
- Oh.
- You see?
Real blood doesn't bead
like that.
They're using cadmium.
Did I take
the hippocratic oath?
No, you took
the hypocritic oath.
Oh, damn!
I thought I did that one.
I'm a dermatologist.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
He's playing hangman
on this guy's belly.
Hmm.
Well, I see by the old clock
on the wall,
it's time
for more boredom.
I'm Harold Lloyd.
- Ooh!
- Ow!
[Grunting]
[All]
Ooh!
Ouch.
Ooh.
- Ooh.
- Ow.
Uhh.
[Laughing]
Look at this shot.
They should
never have let shatner direct.
Sweating like Tom Jones.
That's not unusual.
What's new, pussycat?
Here, would you like
to try this?
It's kind of fun.
Here, I've got to go check
on the sauce there.
Oh, don't wipe the forehead--
the chest, the chest!
What, are you carving,
Pinocchio?
Ow!
♪ Tap heart once,
tap heart twice ♪
Oh, now you've gotta fix
what you've done wrong.
What, are you clamping
every individual cell?
Got the whole
dremel kit out.
Man, this scene is so gross,
even the lighting guy left.
He left a while ago.
- [All groan]
- Oh, please.
It's a gizzard.
Save that for the cat.
Oh, Donald.
Ever operate before?
Nope.
Me, neither.
Ooh, his ink pen
blew up.
Yeah, look at his fingers.
Help me somebody,
please help me.
I shouldn't have had
that Cobb salad for lunch.
You know, they look totally
different when you open them up.
There's no little numbers.
You know, I am completely off
the manual right now.
I have no idea
what I am doing.
It is wild in here.
What are you rooting
around for, tubers?
Close him up.
"Crazy clock,"
the new novel by Henry...
Oh, well.
That was fantastic.
You?
Was it disgusting
for you too?
Kind of looks like
an Annie leibovitz photo.
[Sighs]
I'm spent.
I feel so empty.
Well...
Meanwhile,
at Shakespeare in the park...
[Laughing]
Oh, they're doing "Macbeth."
Gee, I never thought
I'd be grateful
to see this scene again.
Mm-hmm.
- A further warning...
Attention, camp--
tonight's movie
is "my darling Clementine."
If the governments of
all the nations
do not accept my terms...
I will be very put out.
In four days' time,
I will bring
desolation to mankind.
But first, a message from
true value hardware stores.
Meanwhile, euell Gibbons
hears the call of nature.
- Hello!
- [Imitating bird chirping]
Incoming sentence!
[Speaking foreign language]
[Sighs]
That's easy for you to say.
You know, maybe there's some
deep meaning to this movie
that we're just not getting.
Or maybe not.
He's dying
of legionnaire's disease.
- Shriners.
Oh.
Oh yeah.
Don't you wish?
[Chuckles]
Typical shriner, smashed his
midget mustang into a pole.
Yep. Sad, really.
Well, now this con's sneaking
into a petting zoo.
Heavy.
Alexander Monday--
it takes a thief.
I'll take those boots,
Mr. Bond.
How the devil
did I do that?
I couldn't do that again
if I tried.
Did you get close
to the castle?
Close to the castle?
Yes, master.
Jelly donut got away from you,
huh?
Speak.
Woof, woof!
Men guarding the castle.
Oh, great, he's the only one
who knows the plot,
and he's dying.
Typical.
Lisa... still lives.
She's fu manchu's prisoner.
It was Callahan.
Callahan did it.
I have my rights,
I have my rights!
Fu manchu's work is done.
Come on, put on a happy face.
Oh... ohh.
What a lovely tap pant.
Zachoid's headband.
Ackroyd's?
Bury this man with honor.
Uh, right, sir.
I'll put him
in the dumpster.
Oh, no!
Uhh!
Who are you?
Mannix!
[Humming action music]
Let go, you fools!
Tell your men
to drop their arms.
Quickly! Don't move,
any of you.
It could be a trick.
He didn't say Simon says.
I am Omar pasha.
And I'm nayland Smith
of Scotland yard.
I thought I could
smell a policeman.
It seems that for once,
you and I could be
on the same side.
That would be fun.
I, too, seek fu manchu.
Well, gesundheit.
♪♪
We now return to Burt young
in "the Mickey Rooney story."
[Humming]
I'm sorry
I locked us in, okay?
Look, I'm here too.
I'm not happy about it, either!
You have done well,
Dr. Kessler.
His recovery
will take a long time.
We cannot afford to wait
for complete recovery.
It's real pricey.
As soon as he regains
consciousness,
he will be made to talk.
And if heracles refuses, hmm?
Hmm?
Need I remind you, doctor,
that he has
no alternative.
Oh, thanks.
The new light helps.
And if I refuse to help you
any further, hmm?
Then you will sign
this lady's death warrant.
Sure.
Got a pen?
Your help during the operation
was invaluable.
Ooh.
We have no
further use for you.
Oh! No...
Oh! Please, no!
I amuse me.
Ha ha.
Look after your patient,
doctor.
Please.
Watch him well.
Tonight on a very violent
"medical center"...
Curt!
Wait, wait,
you guys got me all wrong.
I'm a veterinary technician!
Father.
"That girl."
...have caught a spy.
Omar pasha.
Alone?
Yes, and unarmed,
as if he
invited capture.
Anything to end the pain.
Have the girl Lisa
brought to me.
Yes, father.
[Singing indistinctly]
I've got a crazy idea,
but it just might--
oh, forget it.
Let me outta here!
Let us outta here.
Oh, it's Paloma Picasso,
right where she belongs.
Who are you?
Anjelica huston.
Lisa.
Did they do that to you?
No, she thought
it would be cute.
Of course they did it.
This movie
is taking its toll on me.
Ohh... me too.
Let's get out of here.
Uhh!
I think this is the worst movie
they've ever made us do.
[Whooshing]
[Thud, creak, zoom]
[Whimpering]
Wow.
That one really stung.
Yeah.
It's a tough one, isn't it?
Yeah, whatever.
Boy, I'd hate
to meet this movie
in a dark alley
some night, huh?
- Yeah.
- Sure, whatever.
Hey, um, Tom,
you got a little--
don't, no, don't.
No, really,
you got a little--
no, just stop it, okay?
Just stop it!
[Whimpering]
Oh, see, this is terrible.
[Muttering incoherently]
Jeepers.
Yo, what's the deal
with fu manchu anyways?
It's not like
he's really evil.
He's just dull!
He's like some twisted
bureaucrat in silk pajamas.
[Whimpers]
It's terrible!
I'm really glad you brought
that up, crow,
because I happen
to have some artist--
[both]
No! No!
Oh, come on.
Come on, it'll add
a little levity, okay?
This is the story of fu manchu,
okay?
I don't care.
Fu manchu was born
Carl Ivan chu
in schenectady,
New York, in 1916.
His parents, David Wayne
and Patricia Ann chu,
owned the superior skate
and blade company,
a thriving ice skate
and cutlery business in 1931.
- Not cutlery!
- Yeah.
Young Carl's father
became very ill,
and they sold the business
and moved the family
to appleton, Wisconsin,
a move that broke his heart.
- Ohh.
- Broke my heart too!
It gets better, though.
It gets better.
Okay... now, okay,
a short year later,
ignoring the pleas
of his heartbroken family,
he moved by himself
to New York City,
the big apple.
His dream: To make it
on Broadway,
the great white way.
Was his dream shattered?
You copied these out
of "the new yorker."
No. He began his career
as most young hopefuls do,
running cigarettes
for Agnes demille.
[Both]
Agnes demille!
- Right.
- Oh, no!
This kept him busy
for 12 hours a day
and nearly
broke his spirit.
It was on one of his many trips
to the store
for a carton of camels
that he hit upon
what was to become
his famous stage name.
The story goes that a panhandler
asked him for a nickel to,
- "get some food, man."
- [Both] Oh, no!
Well, Carl liked that,
and that's all it took.
His name was fu manchu.
Okay?
After a brief stint
running sandwiches
for fatty arbuckle,
he got a job
sweeping the streets
in a clown outfit.
- Not a clown outfit!
- Yep.
- [Both protesting]
- Okay.
No, clowns are fun.
Okay, the idea caught,
and soon,
fu manchu was managing
over a dozen
clown street sweepers.
He was now in a position
to return to his first love,
dinner theater.
I'm going to be sick.
Okay, here we go.
His first role
was as the lovable Betty
in "let's drink a toast
to crazy legs,"
a short-lived,
off-Broadway musical
starring Danny Thomas
and Charles Nelson--
no! No! No!
Oh, what's the use?
Why am I up here?
What are you doing to us?
[All sobbing]
Auntie em!
[Cackling]
Way to go, doc.
[Both]
Whoo!
Yes.
Well, we finally got you
on the run, eh, boobie?
Yeah, frank, there's some pie
in the kitchen.
Why don't you go slice us up
a couple of nice, big slabs
of French silk, huh?
And don't skimp.
Yes, sir!
As for you,
macaulay culkin,
get back into that theater!
Uh, after this message,
of course.
♪♪
[Whimpering]
Oh, man, I don't know.
Yeah.
Gonna make it?
[Whimpering]
He grabbed the girl and turned
her into a guy in a Fez.
He's been eating spaghetti.
Ew.
Hume cronyn.
So you didn't
call a cab then, huh?
Is this the way...
To San Jose.
...stranger in your house.
You are no stranger to me.
Only a friend
I haven't met yet.
But I never thought you
to be a fool.
Fools do not trade...
Fools rush in.
...lives.
Where's she been
all my death?
Give her back to me,
and I will give you the head
of your enemy.
- Alfredo Garcia?
- Enemy?
Nayland Smith.
Release him!
And let him love again.
Heel.
♪ Torn between two lovers ♪
♪ feeling like a-- ♪
Hmm?
My men are camped
in the hills
on the other side of--
he busts out a knife.
...overlooking this castle.
Nayland Smith
is their prisoner.
I want this woman.
Hey, who wouldn't?
She belongs to me.
I have the pink slip.
You shall have her,
provided that you give me
nayland Smith.
You have my word.
Then you shall
remain my guest.
For how long?
That, I shall decide.
You fiend,
you evil, diabolical,
treacherous, wonderful man!
[Humming casually]
Ed ames, you're not.
I was just testing the blade.
I hope you didn't take it
the wrong way!
The girl!
Let her go.
She cannot escape.
Not in those slacks.
Dad, can I borrow the car?
Uh-oh.
Take him to the laboratory.
Feed him to the clam.
Now, uh, where did I
park the...
Ohh.
[Scoffs]
The giraffe--
no.
[Chuckles]
She's really in the dark now.
Hmm...
Sting.
Stung.
Who timed this print,
Stevie wonder?
Whew.
Accepting the award
for editing...
It's "evening at the improv"
with fu manchu.
You are an obstinate man.
Thank you, sir.
How highly do you
value your life
compared with that
of nayland Smith?
Try me.
Ooh, let's crack
the party ball, man.
The entrance to eternity.
Oh, it's plainer than
I thought it would be, hmm.
...which leads directly
to the sea.
Cisterns of water are
poised above it.
A touch of the lever
will release
hundreds of thousands
of gallons of water...
Do it, do it.
And, combined with
professor heracles' crystals,
this can transform
the entire sea
into one gigantic
block of ice.
Which will be great
for parties.
Now then,
the pirates of penzance
will help you
into your chair.
[Gasps]
It's Mrs. Soffel.
Chairman ow.
[Chuckling]
Inside the comic mind,
with fu manchu.
Where is nayland Smith?
Who is nayland Smith?
If you'll free me...
And Lisa.
When we find her.
But, right now, she's doing
a blackout sketch.
My men are camped
in the pass
four kilometers from here.
He's about to become
a pencil-neck geek.
- Uh-oh.
- Nayland Smith is with them.
He's really gonna
needle him.
But wait,
he wasn't done yet.
[Groaning]
I had jell-o today.
Oh, his gums are bleeding.
He doesn't floss much,
does he?
♪♪
Next week on "the castle
of fu manchu."
Stop doing that.
Sorry.
Yeah.
They trying to sneak up
on us?
Hey, just drop the ball
and take a stroke.
For cryin' out loud.
You'll never find it
in that rough.
They're snipe hunting.
Snipe!
At Hazeltine.
You...
You, get in the house.
You're embarrassing me.
It's like the ninja version
of "days of heaven."
Ooh.
Stock footage.
Oh, out, vile jelly.
Where is thy luster now?
Burt young's wardrobe
by Victoria's secret.
He's awake.
Where'd you come from?
I thought
they killed you.
How are you feeling now?
I feel like 100 bucks.
I feel nothing...
But I am alive.
You wish to remain alive,
professor?
Oh, jeez, not him again.
He can suck the air
out of any room.
[Exhales]
You will see
that he stays conscious
for a few more
minutes.
Father, the attack
was successful.
Omar pasha's men
were all destroyed.
Man, your face could launch
a thousand ships.
Nayland Smith?
Dead.
This man saw him killed.
I shall broadcast
at midnight.
On the "king biscuit
flower hour."
He will talk.
You have explained to him
the information
I require from him?
What?
Oh, yes, yes.
Information, yes.
Your task is now completed,
Dr. Kessler.
Oh, these guys.
Ah, come on, dummy.
And how are we feeling?
Go to bed, old man.
The formula, professor.
No.
Hmm... didn't
count on that.
"The castle of fu manchu"
will be back after this.
- That's enough.
- What?
Don't do that anymore.
I'm sick of it.
Welcome to "swing back"
with jazzbo Collins.
It's hot in here!
Then take your clothes off.
Say...
A gentleman never takes
his clothes off in public.
Well, you're no gentleman,
and we're in private.
Oh, uh, so we are.
[Blustering]
Ah, Fez-headed blah.
- [Man vocalizes]
- What on earth did you--
hey, it's Waldo!
They found Waldo.
- Kala.
- Yes, indeed.
My imitation of a lawnmower.
[Coughing]
That was smooth!
[Coughs]
Ohh!
Ohh, ugh...
Rrr!
[Electronic beeping]
This is my ultimatum.
Within the next--
my "hot tomato"?
...the phosphorus
and the city of Istanbul
will be destroyed.
It's not true.
It can't be true!
Dr. Petrie--
Dr. Pee pee?
[Both]
Petrie!
- Ohh.
- Dish.
Nayland Smith.
Nayland Smith is dead.
Long live nayland Smith.
He's dead.
Long live...
Hey, she reached level three
of "super Mario brothers."
Cool.
[Imitates
"super Mario brothers" theme]
Master.
Let me see.
What does this say?
"I'm bald, bite me."
What does that mean?
Wait a minute.
After him!
A formula.
With this, I can control
all things and all men.
But women, hey,
who can control women?
Are you with me on this,
guys, huh?
Flash the signal.
Not the fish, the flash.
Hey, it's spalding gray.
He's having his perfect moment.
Spalding, man!
You're out too far.
This must be
like a triathlon.
You swim, jog, then appear
in a boring movie.
Yeah, well,
I'll have you know
that Roger ebert
liked this film.
Hey, I'll have you know
the only thing Roger ebert likes
is big pans of lasagna.
Lots of them.
Chafe, ooh!
Ooh, chafe!
Ooh, this corduroys.
Ooh, chafe. Chafe.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, chafe.
Ooh. Ah.
Mmm. Mm, mm.
[Imitating kissing]
Bad dreams?
You just kissed the back
of my head.
The worst dreams
are better than reality.
Why?
Think that maybe,
without this awful adventure,
we would never have
realized that we were in love.
Now that
we're going to die,
I could tell you of
a thousand wonderful hours.
I didn't see it.
I didn't want you to see it.
Nobody can see.
I didn't want to distract you
from your work,
your experiments,
your investigations,
which were all
so much
more important than me.
You just kissed me
full on the eyeball.
Exactly right, Ingrid.
Ptuh! Ptuh! Ptuh!
I've got hair
in my mouth.
Thunk!
Ooh, my toe!
Thunk! Oh, my face.
Thanks to those many hours
of hard work
during the professor's
operation,
I managed to gain access
to some acid,
which I can now use...
Against fu manchu.
Oh, well, why didn't you
do this earlier?
He wanted to make time
with a woman.
Ohh.
[Loud sizzling]
Tony Blake is "the magician."
Oh, it's the acid.
Ah, ow!
Stinging!
Agh.
♪♪
Looks like the opening
of "mod squad."
Hmm.
- [Screams]
- Ah, whoops.
Keep quiet.
I shan't hurt you.
I shall.
Fu manchu intends to destroy
Istanbul!
- What?
- Please.
Is there a radio
transmitter?
Yes, I can guide you.
Follow me.
- Father!
- Are they celebrating hanukkah?
Father!
Dr. Kessler and the girl,
they have escaped.
They have
reached the tunnel.
Ohh, ooh.
I've been sitting too long.
Ah, looks like bill Wyman.
It does.
... are released
into the tunnel,
they will die.
Ew.
Powers booth.
- No.
- No?
- Oh.
...managed to break through
to the London frequency.
Not with that etch-a-sketch,
you won't.
[Electronic beeping]
We're through!
I don't love you anymore!
This is nayland Smith,
speaking from fu manchu's
headquarters.
Send a warning
to the phosphorus!
Uh, yeah, right.
Come on, Mickey mouse
broadcasting from Disneyland.
Nayland Smith.
Come on!
We're all getting a little
feedback from those--
those old tube amps
are quirky.
Oh, they are.
Oh, she gained
a little weight.
Mm-hmm.
- Uh-oh.
- It's after 5:00.
The gateway to eternity
is closed!
Yes... yes, dear!
I'm doing it, dear.
Hmm?
- Look!
- What?
You're wonderful.
I could kiss you.
Quick, through the door!
Uh, remember to keep left
for eternity!
Not that way!
That's immortality!
Ohh!
[Sniffs]
Why, it's lemony rosco fog.
- I love that stuff!
- Mmm.
[Sniffs]
Ahh.
The professor!
And Mary Ann!
Come on, professor.
We must get out of here.
Oh, great bedside manner.
Hey, hey,
I'm recovering here.
Get off my bed.
I don't recommend this
for heart patients.
Don't smoke.
Ohh! Ah! Eeh!
It's like one of those
old Duran Duran videos.
Hmm.
Whee!
Ah, he rolls with the punches.
There he goes.
[Sniffs]
Ah.
Nayland Smith
is "marked for"--
now I'm doing it.
Yep.
See?
Oh, this is the worst.
Ah, jeez, you're still here?
Don't smoke.
- Okay, you can smoke.
- Stop it, crow.
- [Grunts]
Ooh.
Thank goodness they
found plywood in that cave.
Yeah.
Come along now.
Time for your sponge bath.
Crotch cam.
Butt cam.
[Chuckles]
Come on!
- I can't make it.
- Keep the scene going!
- Stretch it out!
- Can't make it.
[Grunting]
Hmm?
They have taken heracles.
Come!
Mr. Clean, dead at 35.
Ugh.
Oh, yeah, like
we believe this.
The gate to immortality leads
to the front yard?
Sure.
Flood the tunnels!
♪♪
[Shrieking]
All of a sudden this is like
"flashdance."
Sounds like the water's
falling on a piano.
[Chuckles]
Don't give up.
You've got to fight!
Oh, go ahead,
give up.
Any excuse
to get the girl wet.
[All]
Yep, yep, yep.
[Whimpering]
By this time, my lungs
were aching--
oh, who cares?
This is the trickledown theory
of plots.
So the point of the movie
was to save Burt young?
Ah I guess so.
Nice halter top.
I must go back for Omar!
Come back!
Go.
Women, huh?
Can't live with 'em,
can't live without 'em.
I know.
I hear you.
Let's go get some lunch.
[Panting]
Hey, hey, stay off the carpet
with those dirty shoes!
Hmm?
This is nice.
Filmed in blackface now.
- Mammy!
- Really good.
Oh, she's relaxing in
the green room before the show.
I think I figured out
what this movie is about, guys.
[Both]
What?
Dry ice, rosco fog,
and blood.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's about it.
- Ugh!
- Hey, it's a sewer system.
Where's ed Norton?
Nowhere to be seen.
Aah!
Uh, I didn't
quite catch that.
Could you repeat?
She said, "aah!"
[Both]
Oh.
Oh, god!
Guys, I'd say
this qualifies
as the dark night
of the soul.
Mm-hmm.
[Muttering indistinctly]
Why are we
watching this?
What are we wa--
oh.
Yes, it's "runaway
with the rich and famous."
[Shouting indistinctly]
Well, I'd say her resentments
for fu manchu
are all water
under the bridge.
[Humming]
Ah, these guys
are easy to kill.
They're like mosquitoes.
Don't worry about them.
Mannix.
[Humming]
Ooh.
[Screaming]
We have Paula Abdul's new video
coming up next, on mtv.
[Shrieking]
Yes, you too can relax in
the new hydrojet whirlpool...
Ohh.
Classic captain kirk chop.
Known as a pork chop.
Ohh.
Giant urinal cakes!
Don't eat 'em.
Screamers.
Kessler must have
got through!
The systems have burst.
Oops.
[Explosion]
Let's hide in the miniature
golf course.
MacGyver!
[Coughs]
Wait, I've got muffins
in the oven.
- No!
- Father!
You know, if he was going
to express an emotion,
now would be
the perfect time to do it.
[Laughing]
It's too late.
Father!
Oh, come on,
things are blowing up
that weren't even
in this picture!
Greece,
they just blew up...
Monticello.
Joel, this movie really
isn't very good, is it?
- No, it's not very good.
- Movie sucks, Joel.
It really stinks.
Who's this clown?
The world shall hear
from me again.
Come forward,
cowardly lion!
The world shall
hear from me again.
[All groan]
Fu manchu will be back in
"sweet, sweet"--
oh, who cares?
Oh, look, even
the credits stink.
Oh, I gotta get out of here.
[Sobbing]
Come on.
[Sighs]
I am so depressed.
Okay.
Let's just go.
[Creaking and whooshing]
Okay, well, I...
Guess it's time
to read a letter.
Ah, sure, go ahead.
Like anyone cares.
Okay.
This letter is to Joel,
Servo...
How's, uh...
And crow.
I came back.
Cambot, you wanna put--
oh, what's the use?
[All sobbing]
Well, we've got them on the run
now, frank.
I knew you could do it,
Dr. F.
Here's to the evil
of fu manchu.
No, to the evil
of fu man-you.
Frank, you're the only man
in my organization
that'll talk to me
that way.
Put yourself down
for a honey-glazed ham
and a box of steaks.
Well, actually,
I'm a vegetarian.
Don't know
if I told you.
Nonsense, this is a time
to celebrate.
Put yourself down for
two honey glazed hams.
Well, joely,
you and your cyberpunks
should be ready to admit defeat
right about now.
You haven't won,
Dr. Forrester.
You've lost.
And I feel sorry for you.
You're nothing
but a sad little man
in a hole in the ground
that can only feel power
by hurting others.
- Yeah.
- But we've won,
because we've survived,
and we've survived because,
well, we're Robinsons,
roughly.
And that's what
Robinson do is survive.
Basically, and...
Well, you know what?
If you think it's so easy,
you should give it a try once.
Yeah, you should try to watch
a movie sometime.
You're beginning to sound
like a hallmark card.
Tell you what, maybe
it's the catawba going my head,
but, uh, I'll beat you
at my own experiment.
Heck, we come up with
funnier lines than you guys do.
- [Scoffs]
- Yeah, how hard can it be?
I mean, you know, in school,
I was something
of a class clown.
Absolutely,
let's get the--
you know, at arby's,
when I worked there,
I was so funny,
my nickname was zeppo.
Let's just get the stuff
set up, frank.
All right?
I should warn you, Joel,
I used to be
with the toastmasters.
I'm somewhat of a wry wit
myself.
Ready when you are, cf.
Ah, right.
Roll 'em, frank.
♪♪
Huh. Look at that building.
[Chuckles]
It's big.
- There's-- oh.
- It's huge.
Here comes a car that you could
say something about.
It's so... old.
It's an old car.
Yeah, look at-- oh, and get
a load of this lady.
She's... gonna get out
of that car.
Haikiba.
Yeah, I was gonna say that.
Oh, well, I said it first.
'Cause you could make comments
about these things
that are happening.
Look at her shoes.
Oh, get a load
of those things.
I'm sure.
I'm-- I'm walking
down the street!
[Both laugh]
Now I'm walking down
the hallway.
- Oh...
- She's--
um, uh, what a dickweed.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, bite me.
[Both laugh]
Oh, there's some things
that, really...
That you could
make some comments about.
You certainly could.
You could really--
oh, and she's turning around.
- She maybe--
- we might have--
turn it off.
Turn it off!
Oh, I've had enough.
Well... until next time,
crazy guggenheim.
You know, we could have made
funny comments,
but the movie
wasn't that good.
Fraaa...
[All]
Gotcha!
[All laughing and whooping]
...aaank!
Now I'm going to have to
put your head in a wood vise.
Ah, already
got it started.